<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pollinator Garden on JOJOLENSHOP</title>
    <link>https://jojolen.shop/tags/pollinator-garden/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pollinator Garden on JOJOLENSHOP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jojolen.shop/tags/pollinator-garden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Lobelia Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-lobelia-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-lobelia-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s something quietly radical about choosing to be soft. In a world that prizes speed, productivity, and noise, the gentle presence of &lt;em&gt;Lobelia&lt;/em&gt;—a flower often trailing low or growing in quiet defiance—feels like an act of resilience. As I sit in the company of its cobalt petals or cardinal flames, I often feel this flower sees something in me I’ve only just begun to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lobelia, with its cascading blooms and contemplative hues, is more than ornamental—it’s reflective. It reminds me to grow downward sometimes, to spill over, to be beautiful in the edges and shadows.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Coreopsis Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-coreopsis-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-coreopsis-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-coreopsis-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Coreopsis Varieties&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a quiet rebellion simmering in the golden faces of &lt;strong&gt;Coreopsis&lt;/strong&gt;, a whisper of light that defies the ordinary and invites us to bloom in our own gentle strength. These flowers, also known as &lt;em&gt;tickseed&lt;/em&gt;, hold a unique magic — their radiant yellow petals speak softly but carry a deep story of resilience, healing, and feminine power.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve often found in Coreopsis a tender reminder that the softest voices can cast the longest shadows, that gentle endurance is a form of revolution. For those of us seeking solace in nature’s embrace, these flowers offer not just beauty, but a sanctuary for the soul.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
