<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Slow Living on JOJOLENSHOP</title>
    <link>https://jojolen.shop/tags/slow-living/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Slow Living on JOJOLENSHOP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jojolen.shop/tags/slow-living/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Begonia Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-begonia-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-begonia-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a quiet kind of beauty that doesn’t beg to be seen — it simply is. That is how I feel about begonias.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One sits on my writing desk now, half in shadow, its velvet leaves veined with silver like old secrets. It hasn’t bloomed in months, and yet it soothes me more than any bouquet. In a world that asks us to be loud, bright, and constantly productive, begonias teach a different lesson: to grow gently, in our own time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Impatiens Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-impatiens-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-impatiens-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-impatiens-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Impatiens Varieties&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;&#34;  loading=&#34;lazy&#34; &#xA;alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a quiet magic in the &lt;strong&gt;Impatiens&lt;/strong&gt;—those delicate blossoms that thrive in the cool embrace of shade, whispering stories of resilience, softness, and transformation. To me, these flowers are not just plants; they are companions on the journey of self-discovery and gentle empowerment. They remind us that strength often wears the guise of grace, and beauty blooms best in spaces where care and patience meet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Viola Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-viola-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-viola-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-viola-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Viola Varieties&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some flowers demand to be seen. Viola, instead, invites us to feel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nestled in the hush of spring mornings or beneath a canopy of soft shadows, &lt;em&gt;Viola&lt;/em&gt; (堇菜) appears not with grandeur but with quiet grace—like a whispered thought that lingers in the heart long after it&amp;rsquo;s gone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I first met Viola not in a curated bouquet, but growing wild along the stone path outside a friend’s cottage. Its colors—violet, saffron, milk white—looked like brushstrokes on a dream. I knelt beside it and understood: softness isn’t absence of strength. It’s a different kind of resilience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Daisy Varieties: Blooming Soft Strength and Quiet Resilience</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-daisy-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-daisy-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Where delicate petals carry stories of inner power and tender growth&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a hidden field near my home — a sanctuary only visible to those who move with intention, who listen closely to the whispers between the grass blades. It’s here I first met the daisy, not the perfect bouquet flower, but the wild, unassuming bloom that silently declared:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;“I am here, quietly enough, but fully enough.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a world often dominated by noise and haste, daisies teach us the art of gentle presence — the strength in softness, the resilience in quiet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gentle Strength of Geranium: A Poetic Journey of Growth and Healing</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/geranium-poetic-healing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/geranium-poetic-healing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;“Some flowers are like gentle armor — tender yet unyielding, embracing vulnerability and guarding strength.”&lt;br&gt;&#xA;— Jojo Len&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stepping softly into the world of &lt;strong&gt;geraniums&lt;/strong&gt;, I am greeted by a floral symphony that whispers of womanhood — delicate petals kissed by morning light, yet rooted deep in unwavering resilience. These blooms are more than plants; they are quiet companions in the sacred dance of &lt;strong&gt;growth&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;healing&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;soft power&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this poetic exploration, I invite you to walk beside me through the soulful varieties of Geranium. Together, we’ll uncover how each blossom holds stories of feminine strength, tender endurance, and the grace found in slow, mindful living.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gentle Blossoms: A Zinnia Guide for Your Soulful Garden</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/zinnia-gentle-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/zinnia-gentle-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;gentle-blossoms-a-guide-to-zinnia-varieties-and-an-invitation-to-your-soulful-garden&#34;&gt;Gentle Blossoms: A Guide to Zinnia Varieties and an Invitation to Your Soulful Garden&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this rapidly changing world, the Zinnia stands as a gentle messenger, bringing bright colors and resilient life force to quietly accompany every soul yearning for slow living and inner growth. Their language of flowers symbolizes endurance and joy—just like women who express softness and strength amid the tides of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love watching Zinnias bloom slowly in my garden. It’s a private ritual of feminine self-healing and awakening of strength. They teach me that true resilience does not need noise; gentleness itself is power.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Cosmos: Three Varieties for Joyful, Wild Gardens</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/cosmos-varieties-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/cosmos-varieties-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-cosmos&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Cosmos&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;three-varieties-for-joyful-wild-gardens&#34;&gt;Three Varieties for Joyful, Wild Gardens&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are flowers you plant for structure — neat rows, orderly beds, and controlled shapes.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And then there are flowers like &lt;strong&gt;Cosmos&lt;/strong&gt; — planted for joy, for the breeze, for the soft wildness they bring into our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cosmos flowers embody freedom and lightness.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;They sway gracefully with every whisper of wind, bloom generously without fuss, and remind us that beauty needs no permission. Whether on a sunlit city balcony or a sprawling meadow, Cosmos welcomes you — offering bursts of color, gentle movement, and a quiet celebration of nature’s spontaneity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
