<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plant Therapy on JOJOLENSHOP</title>
    <link>https://jojolen.shop/tags/plant-therapy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Plant Therapy on JOJOLENSHOP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jojolen.shop/tags/plant-therapy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Begonia Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-begonia-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-begonia-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a quiet kind of beauty that doesn’t beg to be seen — it simply is. That is how I feel about begonias.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One sits on my writing desk now, half in shadow, its velvet leaves veined with silver like old secrets. It hasn’t bloomed in months, and yet it soothes me more than any bouquet. In a world that asks us to be loud, bright, and constantly productive, begonias teach a different lesson: to grow gently, in our own time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Snapdragon Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-snapdragon-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-snapdragon-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-snapdragon-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Snapdragon Varieties&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;  &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;“In every snapdragon’s bloom, I hear the quiet roar of a woman learning her own strength — soft yet unyielding, delicate but fierce.”&lt;br&gt;&#xA;— Jojo Len&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a secret garden inside each of us — a sacred space where resilience and tenderness intertwine like vines reaching for the light. Snapdragons, or 龙口花, have been my steadfast companions on this journey of self-discovery and inner healing. Their blossoms, shaped like tiny dragon mouths that whisper ancient stories, invite me to embrace the gentle power of vulnerability and the fierce beauty of softness.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
