<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Garden Journal on JOJOLENSHOP</title>
    <link>https://jojolen.shop/categories/the-garden-journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Garden Journal on JOJOLENSHOP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jojolen.shop/categories/the-garden-journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>8 Popular Rose Varieties &amp; Care Tips for Beginners | Jojo Len</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/rose-varieties-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/rose-varieties-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Roses—often called the queen of flowers—are not only a symbol of romance, but also a favorite of gardeners around the world. For those who are just beginning their gardening journey, understanding the different types of roses and their basic care is the very first step toward creating a slow-living garden of your own.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June Garden Awakening: 5 Herbs That Thrive in Early Summer</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/2025620/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:05:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/2025620/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As June’s light softens the morning, the garden stirs awake—quiet, tender, alive. It is a gentle invitation: to plant, to nurture, to connect deeply with the earth and with yourself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Long-Term Food Storage &amp; Survival Preparedness: A Quiet Act of Care and Strength</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/20255281/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 14:05:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/20255281/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the midst of a world that often feels unsteady, preparing for the future is not just about survival—it is an intimate act of care, a tender way to nurture yourself and those you love. Like planting a garden that will bloom through all seasons, building your food pantry is a soft, deliberate rebellion—a reclaiming of your power and peace.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
