<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jojo Len on JOJOLENSHOP</title>
    <link>https://jojolen.shop/tags/jojo-len/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jojo Len on JOJOLENSHOP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jojolen.shop/tags/jojo-len/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Hollyhock Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-hollyhock-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-hollyhock-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-hollyhock-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Hollyhock Varieties&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a tender magic in the way hollyhocks—&lt;em&gt;Alcea rosea&lt;/em&gt;—rise, tall and proud, like quiet declarations of strength. These flowers have graced gardens for centuries, their towering stalks dotted with blossoms that feel like the petals of a whispered secret or the pages of a well-loved diary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my garden, hollyhocks are companions in the slow work of becoming: patient, resilient, and utterly graceful. They remind me that growth, especially feminine growth, is neither rushed nor linear—it’s a soft unfolding, a gentle insistence on light and space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Phlox Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-phlox-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-phlox-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a quiet poetry in the way flowers bloom—an ancient hymn whispered through petals and leaves. &lt;em&gt;Phlox&lt;/em&gt;, with its clusters of delicate stars, has been my gentle companion through seasons of change, reflection, and growth. Its vibrant colors and tender presence feel like a mirror for the inner landscapes of resilience and feminine strength I nurture within myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;garden-phlox-tall-stories-of-bold-grace&#34;&gt;Garden Phlox: Tall Stories of Bold Grace&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Garden Phlox (&lt;em&gt;Phlox paniculata&lt;/em&gt;) rises with confidence, a beacon of vibrant color and intoxicating fragrance. Varieties like &lt;strong&gt;‘David’&lt;/strong&gt;,&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/jojolen/openpic@main/David3.png?format=webp&#34;  loading=&#34;lazy&#34; &#xA;alt=&#34;Close-up of vibrant deep crimson Garden Phlox ‘David’ flowers with soft pink highlights, showcasing delicate petals and natural texture in warm sunlight, symbolizing passionate feminine strength and resilience.&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Cornflower Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-cornflower-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-cornflower-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Some flowers whisper more than they shout — and some women bloom that way too.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-why-cornflowers-feel-like-coming-home&#34;&gt;🌾 Why Cornflowers Feel Like Coming Home&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s something healing about Cornflowers — those &lt;strong&gt;wild flashes of blue&lt;/strong&gt; that bloom without asking for applause. Known as &lt;em&gt;Centaurea cyanus&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Bachelor’s Button&lt;/strong&gt;, they once thrived at the edges of wheat fields, bold and quiet all at once.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In many ways, they remind me of women I admire — resilient, soft-spoken, deeply rooted.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And on some days, they remind me of myself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Lily Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-lily-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-lily-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-a-gentle-guide-to-lily-varieties&#34;&gt;🌸 A Gentle Guide to Lily Varieties&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lilies are poems the earth writes to the soul.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Each petal is a unique chapter in the feminine story, whispering growth, healing, and strength.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this poetic guide, I invite you to meet nine elegant lilies—each a tender embrace of softness and resilience.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Let their radiant blooms become gentle companions on your journey of self-transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-asiatic-lily-the-courage-of-a-new-flame&#34;&gt;🧡 Asiatic Lily: The Courage of a New Flame&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/jojolen/openpic@main/Asiati1c.png?format=webp&#34;  loading=&#34;lazy&#34; &#xA;alt=&#34;A cluster of bright orange and red Asiatic lilies in full bloom, standing tall in a sunlit garden.&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Nasturtium Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-nasturtium-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-nasturtium-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-the-flower-that-tastes-like-spice-and-grows-like-courage&#34;&gt;🍃 The flower that tastes like spice and grows like courage&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I grew my first nasturtium during a season of uncertainty.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I had no garden—just a cracked terracotta pot and a heart that needed soft things.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The seeds burst open quickly, like they’d been waiting all along.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And when the first red bloom of &lt;em&gt;‘Empress of India’&lt;/em&gt; unfurled, it felt like a whisper from a braver version of myself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nasturtiums (&lt;em&gt;Tropaeolum majus&lt;/em&gt;) aren’t delicate damsels.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;They’re fire-colored, pepper-flavored, and bold-spirited—thriving where the soil is lean and the gardener unsure.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;To grow them is to remember that even in overlooked places, beauty not only survives—it &lt;strong&gt;thrives&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Sweet Pea Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-sweet-pea-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-sweet-pea-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-sweet-pea-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Sweet Pea Varieties&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sweet peas have long been my tender confidants — their fragile petals like soft verses in a whispered poem, their scent a balm for hurried hearts. As I walk among their climbing tendrils, I feel the echo of feminine resilience, the quiet strength that blossoms when softness is embraced, not suppressed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each variety carries a unique voice, a story of growth, healing, and gentle power. Allow me to share my journey through some of the most beloved Sweet Pea varieties, where garden beauty meets the poetry of self-discovery.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Hyacinth Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-hyacinth-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-hyacinth-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-a-gentle-guide-to-hyacinth-varieties&#34;&gt;🌷 A Gentle Guide to Hyacinth Varieties&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A love letter to the flowers that taught me to return to myself.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I first planted hyacinths, I wasn’t seeking color — I was searching for quiet. The garden had become my sanctuary, and hyacinths, with their thick, fragrant blooms, were like reminders in the soil: &lt;strong&gt;that rebirth is slow, and softness is not weakness&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is something deeply feminine about hyacinths. They arrive early, often before the world is ready. They do not wait for permission to bloom. In their fragrant silence, they remind us: you are allowed to take up space — and to smell amazing while doing it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Daffodil Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-daffodil-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-daffodil-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-a-season-of-return-why-i-plant-daffodils-every-year&#34;&gt;🌼 A Season of Return: Why I Plant Daffodils Every Year&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a quiet defiance in the daffodil.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It rises just as the world is still uncertain, the cold not quite gone, the air still tasting of winter’s hush. Yet there she is—a golden flare of hope, rising from cold ground without apology. When I plant daffodil bulbs in the fall, I’m not just gardening. I’m making a soft promise to my future self:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Impatiens Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-impatiens-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-impatiens-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-impatiens-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Impatiens Varieties&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;&#34;  loading=&#34;lazy&#34; &#xA;alt=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;width:100%;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a quiet magic in the &lt;strong&gt;Impatiens&lt;/strong&gt;—those delicate blossoms that thrive in the cool embrace of shade, whispering stories of resilience, softness, and transformation. To me, these flowers are not just plants; they are companions on the journey of self-discovery and gentle empowerment. They remind us that strength often wears the guise of grace, and beauty blooms best in spaces where care and patience meet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Marigold Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/marigold-varieties-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/marigold-varieties-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-marigold-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Marigold Varieties&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;flowers-of-sunlight-roots-of-resilience&#34;&gt;Flowers of Sunlight, Roots of Resilience&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I used to think marigolds were too much—too golden, too obvious.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;But maybe that’s because I was once afraid to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, I see them as soft suns in the garden.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;They are not shy. They bloom where others hesitate.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Their message? &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;You are allowed to take up space.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is my love letter to marigolds, and a gentle guide to their kinds, care, and quiet power.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It’s for the women who speak softly and still shake the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gentle Blossoms: A Zinnia Guide for Your Soulful Garden</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/zinnia-gentle-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/zinnia-gentle-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;gentle-blossoms-a-guide-to-zinnia-varieties-and-an-invitation-to-your-soulful-garden&#34;&gt;Gentle Blossoms: A Guide to Zinnia Varieties and an Invitation to Your Soulful Garden&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this rapidly changing world, the Zinnia stands as a gentle messenger, bringing bright colors and resilient life force to quietly accompany every soul yearning for slow living and inner growth. Their language of flowers symbolizes endurance and joy—just like women who express softness and strength amid the tides of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love watching Zinnias bloom slowly in my garden. It’s a private ritual of feminine self-healing and awakening of strength. They teach me that true resilience does not need noise; gentleness itself is power.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Cosmos: Three Varieties for Joyful, Wild Gardens</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/cosmos-varieties-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/cosmos-varieties-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-cosmos&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Cosmos&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;three-varieties-for-joyful-wild-gardens&#34;&gt;Three Varieties for Joyful, Wild Gardens&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are flowers you plant for structure — neat rows, orderly beds, and controlled shapes.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And then there are flowers like &lt;strong&gt;Cosmos&lt;/strong&gt; — planted for joy, for the breeze, for the soft wildness they bring into our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cosmos flowers embody freedom and lightness.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;They sway gracefully with every whisper of wind, bloom generously without fuss, and remind us that beauty needs no permission. Whether on a sunlit city balcony or a sprawling meadow, Cosmos welcomes you — offering bursts of color, gentle movement, and a quiet celebration of nature’s spontaneity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Lavender Varieties: Perfect Choices for Balcony, Aromatherapy &amp; Garden Bliss</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/lavender-guide-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/lavender-guide-varieties/</guid>
      <description>A soothing yet practical introduction to lavender varieties, helping you choose the perfect lavender for your lifestyle and space. With gentle care tips from Jojo Len.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Tender Sunflowers for Small Gardens &amp; Big Feelings</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/tender-sunflowers-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/tender-sunflowers-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🌻 &lt;strong&gt;Five Tender Sunflowers to Light Up Small Gardens &amp;amp; Big Feelings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sunflowers are more than golden towers in wide-open fields. Some grow softly, quietly — companions to gentle mornings and small rituals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a love letter to five tender sunflower varieties perfect for limited spaces, tender hearts, and healing hands. Let them bloom in your window, on your balcony, or in the small patches where your soul needs light.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to 8 Classic Rose Varieties &amp; Care Tips for Slow Living Gardeners</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-rose-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-rose-varieties/</guid>
      <description>A soft and soulful introduction to eight classic rose varieties, paired with gentle care advice for mindful gardeners who embrace slow living and intentional growth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
