<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jojo Len on JOJOLENSHOP</title>
    <link>https://jojolen.shop/tags/jojo-len/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jojo Len on JOJOLENSHOP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jojolen.shop/tags/jojo-len/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gentle Blossoms: A Zinnia Guide for Your Soulful Garden</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/zinnia-gentle-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/zinnia-gentle-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;gentle-blossoms-a-guide-to-zinnia-varieties-and-an-invitation-to-your-soulful-garden&#34;&gt;Gentle Blossoms: A Guide to Zinnia Varieties and an Invitation to Your Soulful Garden&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this rapidly changing world, the Zinnia stands as a gentle messenger, bringing bright colors and resilient life force to quietly accompany every soul yearning for slow living and inner growth. Their language of flowers symbolizes endurance and joy—just like women who express softness and strength amid the tides of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I love watching Zinnias bloom slowly in my garden. It’s a private ritual of feminine self-healing and awakening of strength. They teach me that true resilience does not need noise; gentleness itself is power.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Cosmos: Three Varieties for Joyful, Wild Gardens</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/cosmos-varieties-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/cosmos-varieties-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-cosmos&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Cosmos&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;three-varieties-for-joyful-wild-gardens&#34;&gt;Three Varieties for Joyful, Wild Gardens&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are flowers you plant for structure — neat rows, orderly beds, and controlled shapes.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And then there are flowers like &lt;strong&gt;Cosmos&lt;/strong&gt; — planted for joy, for the breeze, for the soft wildness they bring into our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cosmos flowers embody freedom and lightness.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;They sway gracefully with every whisper of wind, bloom generously without fuss, and remind us that beauty needs no permission. Whether on a sunlit city balcony or a sprawling meadow, Cosmos welcomes you — offering bursts of color, gentle movement, and a quiet celebration of nature’s spontaneity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Lavender Varieties: Perfect Choices for Balcony, Aromatherapy &amp; Garden Bliss</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/lavender-guide-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/lavender-guide-varieties/</guid>
      <description>A soothing yet practical introduction to lavender varieties, helping you choose the perfect lavender for your lifestyle and space. With gentle care tips from Jojo Len.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Tender Sunflowers for Small Gardens &amp; Big Feelings</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/tender-sunflowers-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/tender-sunflowers-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;🌻 &lt;strong&gt;Five Tender Sunflowers to Light Up Small Gardens &amp;amp; Big Feelings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sunflowers are more than golden towers in wide-open fields. Some grow softly, quietly — companions to gentle mornings and small rituals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a love letter to five tender sunflower varieties perfect for limited spaces, tender hearts, and healing hands. Let them bloom in your window, on your balcony, or in the small patches where your soul needs light.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to 8 Classic Rose Varieties &amp; Care Tips for Slow Living Gardeners</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-rose-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-rose-varieties/</guid>
      <description>A soft and soulful introduction to eight classic rose varieties, paired with gentle care advice for mindful gardeners who embrace slow living and intentional growth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
