<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spring Flowers on JOJOLENSHOP</title>
    <link>https://jojolen.shop/tags/spring-flowers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spring Flowers on JOJOLENSHOP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jojolen.shop/tags/spring-flowers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Crocus Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-crocus-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-crocus-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-gentle-guide-to-crocus-varieties&#34;&gt;A Gentle Guide to Crocus Varieties&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— little poems of color, blooming through the frost&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I still remember the first crocus that rose in my garden — a single purple flame pushing through the cold, half-frozen soil. No fanfare. No audience. Just a soft, certain bloom in a world that hadn’t yet remembered how to be warm.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It didn’t shout. It whispered.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And in that whisper, I heard: &lt;em&gt;Begin, even if the world isn’t ready yet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Hyacinth Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-hyacinth-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-hyacinth-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-a-gentle-guide-to-hyacinth-varieties&#34;&gt;🌷 A Gentle Guide to Hyacinth Varieties&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A love letter to the flowers that taught me to return to myself.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I first planted hyacinths, I wasn’t seeking color — I was searching for quiet. The garden had become my sanctuary, and hyacinths, with their thick, fragrant blooms, were like reminders in the soil: &lt;strong&gt;that rebirth is slow, and softness is not weakness&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is something deeply feminine about hyacinths. They arrive early, often before the world is ready. They do not wait for permission to bloom. In their fragrant silence, they remind us: you are allowed to take up space — and to smell amazing while doing it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Guide to Daffodil Varieties</title>
      <link>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-daffodil-varieties/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jojolen.shop/posts/gentle-guide-to-daffodil-varieties/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;-a-season-of-return-why-i-plant-daffodils-every-year&#34;&gt;🌼 A Season of Return: Why I Plant Daffodils Every Year&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a quiet defiance in the daffodil.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It rises just as the world is still uncertain, the cold not quite gone, the air still tasting of winter’s hush. Yet there she is—a golden flare of hope, rising from cold ground without apology. When I plant daffodil bulbs in the fall, I’m not just gardening. I’m making a soft promise to my future self:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
